Practical Application of Defect Opportunities
Welcome to this session on defect opportunities.
Right now, we're looking at a series of construction standards.
Let's take a look at those, to understand those, we’re going to zero in here.
We have PD, for possible deficiency, AT, acceptable tolerance,
and CR contractor responsibility.
What we are looking at is that portion of the code that is associated with air conditioning.
We’ll make that very bright there.
Air Conditioning and Heating.
So, on row 12, we have a potential deficiency called inadequate heat.
I'll bring that up here. Inadequate heat.
Another, is excessive noise from ducts.
So, when we’re building a home.
We check when we finish for the adequacy of heat
and how quiet it is from the ducts.
Another one is inadequate combustion air vent.
So here what we’re doing again, is we have a set of standards,
workmanship standards, for the state of Arizona
associated with air conditioning and heating for residential homes.
The first one was in adequate heating. Second is excessive noise from ducts.
And third, is inadequate combustion air vent.
Here's another one. The unit is too close to the door.
So you see, each one of these constitutes a defect opportunity.
We could wind up converting this into Sigma capabilities.
We could develop a Sigma capability for air conditioning and heating.
As well as for the entire structure, by pooling them upward.
Again our job here, is to simply look at what constitutes a defect opportunity.
This time we're doing it in the area of construction.
This should be very generalizable to other areas.
Thank you for choosing SSMI.